

REBECCA OVERTON

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

- Pay Area, CA
- □ github.com/overtonr
- m @rebecca-overton

PROFILE

Weeks away from becoming a certified Full Stack Developer, familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 7 years of a wide range of positions where I have been able to demonstrate an excellent work ethic.

SKILLS

Front-End and Back-End Languages & Frameworks MySQL & MongoDB Project Management Problem Solving Visual Design Excellent communication &

collaboration

WORK EXPERIENCE

HOSPITAL ASSISTANT

Dec 2020 - Present

UC San Francisco Health

- -Conduct safety checks on all patients every 15 minutes, using this time to address any patient needs.
- -Assist nurses in treatments, measuring vital signs, and accompanying patients to procedures.
- -Manage medical supplies and placing orders when necessary. Also responsible for coordinating court hearings and file organization of legal documents.

CERTIFIED NURSING ASSISTANT Oct 2019 - May 2020

The Springs at La Jolla Pacific Regent

- Assist residents with activities of daily living in a way that promotes a safe environment. Charting for assigned residents while reporting any significant concerns to the charge nurse.

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

Sequoia Federal Credit Union

Dec 2016 - Aug 2019

- Maintained customer satisfaction with forward-thinking strategies focused on addressing customer needs and resolving concerns regarding financial information.
- Led projects such as transferring documentation into a new database, testing features before offering them to our members, and creating monthly newsletters.

STOCK LEAD

Hollister Co.

Jul 2015 - Dec 2018

- Supervised stock crew associates in daily replenishment, storage management and merchandising.
- Maintained customer satisfaction with professional handling of product inquiries and transactions.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Coding Certification *UC Berkeley Extension*

Sep 2022 - Dec 2022

BS Developmental Psychology *UC San Diego*

Jan 2016 -Dec 2017

HS DIPLOMA, HIGHEST HONORS Sep 2012 - May 2016

Alma Heights Christian Academy